<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Supatsara Wattanakriengkrai, Bodin Chinthanet, Hideaki Hata, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Christoph Treude, Jin Guo, and Kenichi Matsumoto, GitHub Repositories with Links to Academic Papers: Open Access, Traceability, and Evolution, Journal of Systems and Software, Vol. 183, 111117, January 2022. [Dataset] (JCR: 3.514 in 2021) (Journal First at ICSME 2022)
Hideaki Hata, Nicole Novielli, Sebastian Baltes, Raula Gaikovina Kula, and Christoph Treude, GitHub Discussions: An Exploratory Study of Early Adoption, Empirical Software Engineering, Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Pacawat Kangwanwisit, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, Rungroj Maipradit, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, A component recommendation model for issues in software projects, In Proc. of 19th International Joint Conference on Computer Science and Software Engineering (JCSSE 2022), pp. 1-6, June 2022.
Saranphon Phaithoon, Supakarn Wongnil, Patiphol Pussawong, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, Rungroj Maipradit, Hideaki Hata, ‪and Kenichi Matsumoto, FixMe: A GitHub Bot for Detecting and Monitoring On-Hold Self-Admitted Technical Debt, In Proc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: An fMRI Study with Expert Programmers, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.
Takeshi D. Itoh, Takatomi Kubo, Kiyoka Ikeda, Yoshiharu Ikutani, Yuki Maruno, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, and Kazushi Ikeda, Contrasting Human and Machine Intelligence for Program Comprehension, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
