<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Mingyu Guo, Guanhua Wang, Hideaki Hata, and Muhammad Ali Babar, Revenue maximizing markets for zero-day exploits, Autonomous Agents and Multi-Agent Systems, Vol. 35, Issue 2, Article No. 36, October 2021. (JCR: 2.475 in 2021)
Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Expert programmers have fine-tuned cortical representations of source code, eNeuro, Vol. 8, No. 1, ENEURO.0405-20.2020, January/February 2021. [Dataset] (JCR: 4.081 in 2020)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Pacawat Kangwanwisit, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, Rungroj Maipradit, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, A component recommendation model for issues in software projects, In Proc. of 19th International Joint Conference on Computer Science and Software Engineering (JCSSE 2022), (to appear).
Hideaki Hata, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Takashi Ishio, and Christoph Treude, Research Artifact: The Potential of Meta-Maintenance on GitHub, In Proc. of 43rd IEEE/ACM International Conference on Software Engineering: Companion Proceedings (ICSE-Companion 2021), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: An fMRI Study with Expert Programmers, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.
Takeshi D. Itoh, Takatomi Kubo, Kiyoka Ikeda, Yoshiharu Ikutani, Yuki Maruno, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, and Kazushi Ikeda, Contrasting Human and Machine Intelligence for Program Comprehension, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
