<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hideaki Hata | NAIST</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hideaki Hata | NAIST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A topology of npm ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/figure/apsec2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/figure/apsec2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/abstract/</guid>
      <description>I am an Assistant Professor in Graduate School of Information Science at Nara Institute of Science and Technology, Japan. I am a member of Software Engineering Laboratory. I received M.Sc. Ph.D degrees in Graduate School of Information Science and Technology from Osaka University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>photo</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/photo/photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/photo/photo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MarioLike game performance visualization</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/figure/vissoft2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/figure/vissoft2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent papers</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/news/</guid>
      <description>Nuttapon Lertwittayatrai, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Saya Onoue, Hideaki Hata, Arnon Rungsawang, Pattara Leelaprute, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Extracting Insights from the Topology of the Javascript Package Ecosystem, In Proc. of 24th Asia-Pacific Software Engineering Conference (APSEC2017). See [Figure].
 Koji Kitagawa, Mingyu Guo, Kiminao Kogiso, and Hideaki Hata, Utility Design for Two-Player Normal-Form Games, In Proc. of 2017 Asian Control Conference (ASCC 2017).
 Hideaki Hata, Mingyu Guo, and Ali Babar, Understanding the Heterogeneity of Contributors in Bug Bounty Programs, In Proc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/service/</guid>
      <description> Journal  Associate Editor  IEICE Transactions on Information and Systems (2017-)  Reviews  Journal of Systems and Software IEICE Transactions on Information and Systems IEEE Transactions on Services Computing   Conference  2018  APSEC (Local arrangement), SEmotion (PC member), IWESEP (Steering member)  2017  COMPSAC (PC member), SANER (ERA track review), APSEC (Short papers and posters track review), CHASE (PC member), SEmotion (PC member), IWESEP (Steering member), BCD (Publicity co-chairs and PC member)  2016  COMPSAC (PC member), SANER (Tool track review, ERA track review, and Local arrangement), MSR (PC member), CHASE (PC member), IWESEP (General chair)  2015  COMPSAC (PC member)  2014  COMPSAC (PC member), IWESEP (PC member), SERA (PC member)  2013  IWESEP (Tutorial chair and PC member)  2012  IWESEP (PC member)  2011  IWESEP (PC member)  2010  IWESEP (PC member)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/publications/</guid>
      <description>Conference Proceedings  Keitaro Nakasai, Hideaki Hata, Saya Onoue, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Analysis of Donations in Eclipse Project, In Proc. of 8th IEEE International Workshop on Empirical Software Engineering in Practice (IWESEP 2017), pp. 18-22, March 2017.
 Tetsuya Kanda, Mingyu Guo, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Towards Understanding an Open-Source Bounty: Analysis of Bountysource, In Proc. of 24th IEEE International Conference on Software Analysis, Evolution, and Reengineering (SANER 2017), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>