<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Rungroj Maipradit, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Sentiment Classification Using N-Gram Inverse Document Frequency and Automated Machine Learning, IEEE Software, Special Issue on Sentiment and Emotion in Software Engineering, Vol. 36, No. 5, pp. 65-70, September 2019. (JCR: 2.589 in 2019)
  Keitaro Nakasai, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Are Donation Badges Appealing? A Case Study of Developer Responses to Eclipse Bug Reports, IEEE Software, Special Issue on Managing Software Platforms and Ecosystems, Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Noppadol Assavakamhaenghan, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Suppawong Tuarob, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Hideaki Hata, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Software Team Member Configurations: A Study of Team Effectiveness in Moodle, In Proc. of 10th International Workshop on Empirical Software Engineering in Practice (IWESEP 2019), pp. 19-24, December 2019.
  Supatsara Wattanakriengkrai, Napat Srisermphoak, Sahawat Sintoplertchaikul, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Automatic Classifying Self-Admitted Technical Debt Using N-Gram IDF, In Proc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: An Fmri Study with Expert Programmers, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.
  Takeshi D. Itoh, Takatomi Kubo, Kiyoka Ikeda, Yoshiharu Ikutani, Yuki Maruno, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, and Kazushi Ikeda, Contrasting Human and Machine Intelligence for Program Comprehension, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>