<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Hideaki Hata | NAIST</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Hideaki Hata | NAIST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/section/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/abstract/</guid>
      <description>I am an Assistant Professor in Graduate School of Information Science at Nara Institute of Science and Technology, Japan. I am a member of Software Engineering Laboratory. I received M.Sc. Ph.D degrees in Graduate School of Information Science and Technology from Osaka University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New papers</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/news/</guid>
      <description>Hideaki Hata, Mingyu Guo, and Ali Babar, Understanding the Heterogeneity of Contributors in Bug Bounty Programs, In Proc. of 11th ACM / IEEE International Symposium on Empirical Software Engineering and Measurement (ESEM 2017).
 Nuttapon Lertwittayatrai, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Saya Onoue, Hideaki Hata, Arnon Rungsawang, Pattara Leelaprute, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Extracting Insights from the Topology of the Javascript Package Ecosystem, In Proc. of 24th Asia-Pacific Software Engineering Conference (APSEC2017). See Figure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/section/publications/</guid>
      <description>Conference Proceedings  Katsuya Ogami, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Hideaki Hata, Takashi Ishio, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Using High-Rising Cities to Visualize Performance in Real-Time, In Proc. of 5th IEEE Working Conference on Software Visualization (VISSOFT 2017), 33-42, September 2017. See Figure, Tool, Slides, Video 1, and Video 2.
 Pannavat Terdchanakul, Hideaki Hata, Passakorn Phannachitta, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Bug or Not? Bug Report Classification using N-Gram Idf, In Proc. of 33rd IEEE International Conference on Software Maintenance and Evolution (ICSME 2017), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>