<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Katsuya Ogami, Keitaro Nakasai, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Heijo: A Real-Time Profiler for Java and Android Applications with City-Like Visualization of Dynamic Code Executions, Computer Software, Vol. 36, No. 2, pp. 93-105, April 2019. (in Japanese)
 Kyohei Uemura, Keitaro Nakasai, Katsuya Ogami, Hideaki Hata, Tomohiro Ichinose, Kenichi Matsumoto, and Hajimu Iida, Codosseum : A Web Service for Supporting Development and Analysis of Open Source Software Projects, Computer Software, Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Noppadol Assavakamhaenghan, Morakot Choetkiertikul, Suppawong Tuarob, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Hideaki Hata, Chaiyong Ragkhitwetsagul, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Software Team Member Configurations: A Study of Team Effectiveness in Moodle, In Proc. of 10th International Workshop on Empirical Software Engineering in Practice (IWESEP 2019), pp. 19-24, December 2019.
 Supatsara Wattanakriengkrai, Thanwadee Sunetnanta, and Hideaki Hata, Automatic Classifying Self-Admitted Technical Debt Using N-Gram IDF, In Proc. of 26th Asia-Pacific Software Engineering Conference (APSEC 2019), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Supatsara Wattanakriengkrai, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Identifying Publication Citations in Source Code Comments Using Bert, 10th International Workshop on Empirical Software Engineering in Practice (IWESEP 2019), Poster session, December 2019.
 Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: an Fmri Study with Expert Programmers, APSIPA BioSiPS Workshop 2019, Poster session, August 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>