<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Yoshiki Higo, Shinpei Hayashi, Hideaki Hata, and Meiyappan Nagappan, Ammonia: An Approach for Deriving Project Specific Bug Patterns, Empirical Software Engineering, Vol. 25, No. 3, pp. 1951-1979, May 2020. [Tool] (JCR: 3.156 in 2019) (Journal First at ICSE 2021)
  Yusuf Sulistyo Nugroho, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, How Different Are Different Diff Algorithms in Git?, Empirical Software Engineering, Vol. 25, No. 1, pp. 790-823, January 2020. [Dataset], [Slides], and [Video] (JCR: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Hideaki Hata, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Takashi Ishio, Christoph Treude, Research Artifact: The Potential of Meta-Maintenance on GitHub, In Proc. of 43rd IEEE/ACM International Conference on Software Engineering: Companion Proceedings (ICSE-Companion 2021), pp. 192-193, May 2021.
  Rungroj Maipradit, Bin Lin, Csaba Nagy, Gabriele Bavota, Michele Lanza, Hideaki Hata, and Kenichi Matsumoto, Automated Identification of On-hold Self-admitted Technical Debt, In Proc. of 20th IEEE International Working Conference on Source Code Analysis and Manipulation (SCAM 2020), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: An fMRI Study with Expert Programmers, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.
  Takeshi D. Itoh, Takatomi Kubo, Kiyoka Ikeda, Yoshiharu Ikutani, Yuki Maruno, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, and Kazushi Ikeda, Contrasting Human and Machine Intelligence for Program Comprehension, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
