<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Hideaki Hata</title>
    <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Hideaki Hata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>Tao Xiao, Sebastian Baltes, Hideaki Hata, Christoph Treude, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Takashi Ishio, and Kenichi Matsumoto, 18 Million Links in Commit Messages: Purpose, Evolution, and Decay, Empirical Software Engineering, Vol. 28, Issue 4, Article No. 91, May 2023. [Dataset] (JCR: 4.1 in 2022).&#xA;Hideaki Hata, Yusuke Hara, and Taiki Todo, Applications of Multi-Agent Systems Research for Transportation Systems, SYSTEMS, CONTROL AND INFORMATION, Vol. 67, Issue 1, pp. 18-24, January 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/conference/</guid>
      <description>Christoph Treude and Hideaki Hata, She Elicits Requirements and He Tests: Software Engineering Gender Bias in Large Language Models, In Proc. of 20th International Conference on Mining Software Repositories (MSR 2023), pp. 624-629, May 2023. [Dataset] (Acceptance rate: 37.4%)&#xA;Dong Wang, Tao Xiao, Christoph Treude, Raula Gaikovina Kula, Hideaki Hata, and Yasutaka Kamei, Understanding the Role of Images on Stack Overflow, In Proc. of 20th International Conference on Mining Software Repositories (MSR 2023), pp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hideakihata.github.io/publications/others/</guid>
      <description>Youmei Fan, Dong Wang, Supatsara Wattanakriengkrai, Hathaichanok Damrongsiri, Christoph Treude, Hideaki Hata, and Raula Gaikovina Kula, Going Viral: Case Studies on the Impact of Protestware, 46th IEEE/ACM International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE 2024), Poster session, April 2024.&#xA;Yoshiharu Ikutani, Takatomi Kubo, Satoshi Nishida, Hideaki Hata, Kenichi Matsumoto, Kazushi Ikeda, and Shinji Nishimoto, Toward Identifying the Neural Basis of Programming Expertise: An fMRI Study with Expert Programmers, 20th Winter Workshop on Mechanism of Brain and Mind, Poster session, January 2020.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
